Thank you. We're going to slow things down for
you for just a minute.
The streetlights make a blurry line.
I'm running through the same old signs.
I'm just a face in a passing crowd
Afraid to speak my thoughts out loud
But then you found me in the noise
You heard a whisper in my voice
You gave me something to believe,
a reason I wouldn't
If you walked away, the sky would lose its blue. I
wouldn't know what to do. I'd be lost in the gray.
If you walked away, my world would fall apart.
You're the owner of my heart.
They build these walls so high and steep
With promises they never keep
But we have a fortress, strong and true
I'm safe as long as I have you. If you walked away,
the sky would lose its blue. I wouldn't know what
to do. I'd be lost in the gray. If you walked away,
my world would fall apart.
You're the owner of my neon heart
I'm holding on, I'm holding tight Don't let me go
into the night
If you walked away The sky would lose its blue I
wouldn't know what to do I'd be lost in the gray If
you walked away My world would fall apart
You're the owner of my heart
Don't walk away Thank
you so much